# Andrey Turbov Sep 5, 1996

#### Contact

Phone: +7 (999) 215-6653 E-mail: unsip@tutamail.com Github: https://github.com/unsip

LinkedIn: Andrey Turbov

I'm a software engineer with a few years of DevOps expertise. Self-education is of the highest value for me, which I'm always striving. Not only because regular studies got me into the industry, but also because I appreciate scientific endeavour and enjoy exploring world of abstract ideas. Hence, I'm looking forward to further improve my skills in software craftsmanship, giving my preference to interesting C++ projects. The essential job-aspect for me is to acquire expertise in solving challenging problems using modern technologies and practices. My experience in an international environment enables me to get along with foreign co-workers and customers quickly. In my spare time, I enjoy studying humanities, learning computer graphics, playing board games, and contemplating on aesthetically pleasing art.

# **Employment**

**T-Systems**Software Developer

2020 — present
St. Petersburg

- Full stack maintainance and development of internal platform for executing and monitoring various bots
- Project architecture revision and design using UML diagrams
- Proposed solution prototyping along with introduction of Python RPC framework
- Held skill sharing meetings with colleagues

2018 — 2020 St. Petersburg

Software Configuration Manager

- Regular presentations on international on-site meetings
- Implemented and maintained internal services and utilities such as:
  - Custom dashboard web service for project environments
  - Web service for generating delivery instructions for production OPS
  - CLI utility for complex application configuration management
- Designed and developed an orchestration solution using Puppet and Puppet Bolt
- Legacy CI/CD infrastucture maintainance and refactoring
- Support for international DEV, QA and production OPS teams

#### Education

2014 - 2016	Saint Petersburg State University of Aerospace Instrumentation, Depart-
	ment of Computer Science
2013 - 2014	Peter the Great Saint-Petersburg Polytechnic University, Department of
	Physics and Astronomy

## **Used Tools**

Programming languages: Python, C++(11/14/17), JavaScript (ES6)

Frameworks: Django, Flask, ReactJS, RPyC

Development utilities: Git, Bash, core \*nix utilities

Operating systems: Linux (RHEL, Debian, Arch, Gentoo)

Build systems and CI/CD: Make, CMake, Gitlab CI, Jenkins

Containers/Virtualization: Docker, Vagrant, VirtualBox

Infrastructure orchestration: Ansible, Puppet, Bolt

Monitoring: ELK stack, Grafana, Prometheus

Webservers: Nginx, Apache

Databases: PostgreSQL, OracleDB

## Other

Languages: English upper-intermediate, Russian native

Achievements: participated in student physics and astronomy conferences/competitions, completed MIT

GSL program at ITMO university

Hobbies: programming, philosophy, generative art, spider keeping